dickeys.com 2017-01-30

# P

                                         PRIVACY POLICY
Dickey’s Commitment to Privacy:
At Dickey’s Barbecue Restaurants, Inc. (“Dickey’s”), we understand that our customers are
concerned about the use of their personal information, and we respect our customers’ privacy. This
Privacy Policy explains the steps we have taken to ensure that the personal information you submit
to us is secure and kept confidential.
Additionally, Dickey’s may act as a “landing page” to other sites. This Privacy Policy expressly
applies only to this site and not any third-party sites accessed via third-party or other links.
The Information Dickey’s Requests:
When you register on our site, make a purchase request, or consent to participating in a Dickey’s
promotion, Dickey’s collects and stores the following types of information:
         Name
         Address
         E-mail address
         Telephone Number
         Credit/Debit Card Information*
*Credit/Debit Card Information is not stored by Dickey’s. Credit/Debit Card Information is
collected for the purpose of completing your purchase order and transmitted to Stripe (Spark
Intelligence) for processing.
Dickey’s requires the above information to provide the goods and services that you request and to
let you know of additional goods and services about which you might be interested. We may also
use this information to customize your experience using our website. If you are purchasing goods
and services on Dickey’s website as a gift to be sent directly to the recipient, Dickey’s shall also
request the recipient’s name, address, telephone number, and email address.
Dickey’s may ask you to provide personal information at other times, such as if you enter a
promotion, communicate with us, or complete a survey. If you choose to receive information
regarding Dickey’s promotions, then you give us your consent to share your name and email
address with the third party offering the promotion or the third party who may forward marketing
or other materials on our behalf. If you wish to discontinue receiving promotional email from
Dickey’s, you may unsubscribe at any time by clicking the “Unsubscribe” link located at the
bottom       of      the      promotional       message       or      contacting      Dickey’s    at
communicationservices@dickeys.com.
Dickey’s may gather general statistical information about our website and visitors, such as IP
addresses, browsers, pages viewed, number of visitors, goods and services purchased, and

transactions completed using cookies and tags. Additionally, this information is used to better
serve you with appropriate and relevant marketing offers. Cookies are small files that your Web
browser places on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies are not used to access information entered
on the secure server; this information can only be accessed when you enter your name and
password.
Dickey’s, and/or our third-party advertising service providers or other third-party vendors, may
place cookies or similar files on your computer for security purposes (such as authentication), to
facilitate site navigation and to personalize your experience while visiting our Site. Cookies allow
us to collect technical and navigational information, such as browser type, time spent on our Site
and pages visited (these types of cookies are typically referred to as “Session Cookies”). We also
use cookies that enable us to serve advertisements of our products and services, including special
offers, when you visit other websites (these cookies may be referred to as “Advertising Cookies”).
How Your Information is Used:
Dickey’s goal is to provide its customers with the best products to meet their needs, so we evaluate
your personal interactions with us in an effort to bring you Dickey’s products which best suit your
individual tastes. We also use your information to improve our marketing and promotional efforts,
to statistically analyze site usage, to improve our content and product offerings, and to customize
our site’s content, layout, and services.
We may use your information to deliver Dickey’s product and promotional information that is
targeted to your interests. At times, we may ask you to voluntarily provide us with additional
information regarding your personal or business interests, experience, or requests, which we may
use to customize our products and services for you.
The email addresses that Dickey’s collects are used by use to contract consumers for marketing
purposes that are not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes.
You may receive periodic promotional mailings or phone calls from Dickey’s at the postal address
and telephone number provided to us. If you would prefer not to receive such promotional offers,
please call Dickey’s at 972.248.9899 or email us at communicationservices@dickeys.com.
If you place a request for products or services, we use your personal information to ship your order.
If the order for products or services is fulfilled from a retail partner, we may provide your relevant
information to that retailer for the purposes of the transaction.
Dickey’s may contract with a third party advertising partner or other third-party vendor to serve
ads or make other offers or provide other services on our behalf across the Internet and sometimes
on this website. Such third party advertising partners may collect anonymous information about
your visits to Dickey’s website and your interactions with our products and services. Some
information we disclose may include the information you provided to us in completing your

transaction on Dickey’s website. Our advertising partner makes the date we provide anonymous
and does not use your personal information, such as your name, address, email address, etc., in
order to deliver advertising to you that is tailored to your interests.
To choose not to have your transactional information given to, or used by, our third-party
advertising partner in this way, please contact communicationservices@dickeys.com.
We may also use or disclose information to resolve dispute or investigate problems. We may
disclose or access information whenever we believe in good faith that the law so requires or if we
otherwise consider it necessary to do so to maintain service and improve our products and services.
We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, to manage our website,
and to enhance our site based on the usage pattern data we receive.
Security:
Dickey’s is committed to preventing the unauthorized access to your personal information
provided to us via our website, and we maintain procedures and technology designed for this
purpose. Dickey’s takes the following steps to protect the information that you provide us: (1) we
update and test our technology on a regular basis in order to improve the protection of customer
information; and (2) we require outside customers and independent contractors to whom we
provide customer information for marketing and servicing or processing purposes to restrict the
use of your information to those purposes and we prohibit independent use of such information.
Children’s Online Privacy Act:
Dickey’s does not knowingly collect or use personal information from children under 13 without
first obtaining verifiable consent form their parents. We have not way of distinguishing the age of
individuals who visit our website, and so we follow the same Privacy Policy for individuals of all
ages. If a child has provided us with personal information without parental or guardian consent,
the parent or guardian should contact us to remove the information and opt out of promotional
opportunities. For more information about the Children’s Online Privacy Act, please visit the
Federal Trade Commission website at www.ftc.gov.
Consent and Changes to Dickey’s Privacy Policy:
By using Dickey’s website, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information
by Dickey’s. The practices and policies contained in this disclosure are subject to change. If we
ever change our practices and policies, we will post any changes on this page so that you always
are aware of the information that we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we
disclose it. The practices and policies in this disclosure replace all previous notices or statements
with respect to the same subject matter.

How to Contact Dickey’s:
To update, correct, or delete your personal information, you may contact us at:
       Dickey’s Barbecue Restaurants, Inc.
       Marketing Department
       4514 Cole Avenue, Suite 1015
       Dallas, Texas 75025
       972.248.9899
       communicationservices@dickeys.com
To protect your privacy and security, we also will take reasonable steps to verify your identity
before granting access or making corrections or changes.
